[
  {
    "id": "472",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "EC2",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 2",
      "question": "What are the two types of volume stores for EC2 instances?",
      "answers": [
        "EBS backed volumes",
        "Instance Store backed volumes",
        "RAID backed volumes",
        "EFS backed volumes",
        "Local Store backed volumes"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": ["EBS backed volumes", "Instance Store backed volumes"]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "473",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "EC2",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "Instance store volumes are somtimes called what?",
      "answers": [
        "ephemeral storage",
        "temporary storage",
        "solid state storage",
        "permanent storage"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": ["ephemeral storage"]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "474",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "EC2",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "Instance store volumes can be _____?",
      "answers": [
        "stopped",
        "started",
        "copied",
        "replicated"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": ["stopped"]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "475",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "EC2",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "If the underlying host fails, you will _____ when using Instance store backed volumes?",
      "answers": [
        "lose your data",
        "retain your data",
        "not be impacted"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": ["lose your data"]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "476",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "EC2",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "_____ backed volumes can be stopped?",
      "answers": [
        "EBS",
        "Instance Store"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": ["EBS"]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "477",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "EC2",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "If the EC2 instance is stopped, you will _____ when using EBS backed volumes?",
      "answers": [
        "lose your data",
        "not lose your data"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": ["not lose your data"]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "478",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "EC2",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "If you reboot your EC2 instance you will not lose your data for which type of volumes?",
      "answers": [
        "EBS backed",
        "Instance Store backed",
        "you won't lose data for either"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": ["you won't lose data for either"]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "479",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "EC2",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "By default, if you terminate your EC2 instance your root volumes will be deleted for which types?",
      "answers": [
        "EBS backed",
        "Instance Store backed",
        "both types will be deleted"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": ["both types will be deleted"]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "480",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "EC2",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "For this type, you can tell AWS to keep the root volume (through the console) if you terminate your EC2 instance?",
      "answers": [
        "EBS backed",
        "Instance Store backed",
        "both types will be deleted"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": ["EBS backed"]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "481",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "EC2",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 3",
      "question": "What are the three types of Elastic Load Balancers?",
      "answers": [
        "Classic",
        "Application",
        "Network",
        "Ephemeral"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": ["Classic", "Application", "Network"]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "482",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "EC2",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "Which type of load balancer operates at layer 7?",
      "answers": [
        "Classic",
        "Application",
        "Network",
        "Ephemeral"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": ["Application"]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "483",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "EC2",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "Which type of load balancer operates at layer 4?",
      "answers": [
        "Classic",
        "Application",
        "Network",
        "Ephemeral"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": ["Classic"]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "484",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "EC2",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "Which type of load balancer makes routing decisions at the application layer (HTTP/HTTPS)?",
      "answers": [
        "Classic",
        "Application",
        "Network",
        "Ephemeral"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": ["Application"]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "485",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "EC2",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "Which type of load balancer supports path-based routing?",
      "answers": [
        "Classic",
        "Application",
        "Network",
        "Ephemeral"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": ["Application"]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "486",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "EC2",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "Which type of load balancer can route requests to one or more ports on each EC2 instance or container instance in your VPC?",
      "answers": [
        "Classic",
        "Application",
        "Network",
        "Ephemeral"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": ["Application"]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "487",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "EC2",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "Which type of load balancer makes routing decisions at either the transport layer (TCP/SSL) or the application layer (HTTP/HTTPS)?",
      "answers": [
        "Classic",
        "Application",
        "Network",
        "Ephemeral"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": ["Classic"]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "488",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "EC2",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "Which type of load balancer supports either EC2-Classic or VPC?",
      "answers": [
        "Classic",
        "Application",
        "Network",
        "Ephemeral"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": ["Classic"]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "489",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "EC2",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "You get a public IP address for your load balancer?",
      "answers": [
        "true",
        "false"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": ["false"]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "490",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "EC2",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "What do you get when you create an ELB that allows you to point traffic to your EC2 instances behind the ELB?",
      "answers": [
        "a DNS name",
        "the public IP address",
        "an elastic IP address"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": ["a DNS name"]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "491",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "EC2",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 2",
      "question": "What are the two statuses reported for EC2 instances monitored by ELB?",
      "answers": [
        "InService",
        "OutofService",
        "OffLine",
        "OnLine"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": ["InService", "OutofService"]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "492",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "EC2",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "ELB health checks check the health of the EC2 instances they front by 'talking to the EC2 instances' over __________?",
      "answers": [
        "HTTP or HTTPS",
        "TCP",
        "SSL",
        "HTML"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": ["HTTP or HTTPS"]
    }
  }
]
